export const intPast =[{
         "id": 1,
         "question": "Mozart _________ more than 600 pieces of music.",
         "options": [
             "write",
             "writed",
             "wrote",
             "written"
         ],
         "answer": "wrote"
     },
     {
         "id": 2,
         "question": "'How _________ to play the piano so well?' 'My dad taught me.'",
         "options": [
             "did you learn",
             "are you learning",
             "did you learned",
             "did learn you"
         ],
         "answer": "did you learn"
     },
     {
         "id": 3,
         "question": "The movie wasn't good. _________ it at all.",
         "options": [
             "I didn't enjoyed",
             "I do enjoy",
             "I did enjoy",
             "I didn't enjoy"
         ],
         "answer": "I didn't enjoy"
     },
     {
         "id": 4,
         "question": "I _________ home last night when I met Christian.",
         "options": [
             "was walking",
             "walked",
             "were walking",
             "walk"
         ],
         "answer": "was walking"
     },
     {
         "id": 5,
         "question": "Jack _________ his back while he was working in the garden.",
         "options": [
             "was hurting",
             "was hurted",
             "hurt",
             "hurted"
         ],
         "answer": "hurt"
     },
     {
         "id": 6,
         "question": "What _________ this time yesterday?",
         "options": [
             "did you do",
             "you were doing",
             "were you doing",
             "did you did"
         ],
         "answer": "were you doing"
     },
     {
         "id": 7,
         "question": "When I last saw Amy she _________ her daugher's birthday party.",
         "options": [
             "was planned",
             "was planning",
             "planned",
             "is planning"
         ],
         "answer": "was planning"
     },
     {
         "id": 8,
         "question": "It was so hot I _________ my coat.",
         "options": [
             "took off",
             "taked off",
             "take off",
             "taken off"
         ],
         "answer": "took off"
     },
     {
         "id": 9,
         "question": "The window was open and a wasp _________.",
         "options": [
             "fly in",
             "flied in",
             "flew in",
             "flown in"
         ],
         "answer": "flew in"
     },
     {
         "id": 10,
         "question": "Kate _________ a cake when we walked in.",
         "options": [
             "was decorate",
             "decorated",
             "was decorating",
             "decorating"
         ],
         "answer": "was decorating"
     }
 ]